Oh!
Heh heh heh heh
Update status
Fucked up and dry gums.
So...
I'm Fuyuka Saito of Sakurazaka46.
I'm now, ta-da!
Can you tell?
I'm here at Seodori Kaikan.
What a surprise, we are in Tokushima Prefecture!
Wow!
Yes, this is the building that represents the umbrella that the Ao-odori dancers wear when they dance,
Like this, we are really in Tokushima Prefecture.
So, for this project, I danced the Ao-odori in Tokushima Prefecture, the home of the Ao-odori!
Yay!
I did Ao-odori when I was in elementary and junior high school,
I have never danced in Tokushima prefecture,
I was wondering if you could let me dance on this YouTube page as a project,
I asked for it and it came true.
I'm a little nervous now,
I'm going to go!
So, this is the person who will be helping me today.
I'm Hei Saito of Sakurazaka 46.
My name is Heika Saito from Sakurazaka 46.
I'm Heika Saito from Sakurazaka 46, and I'm looking forward to working with you today.
I actually used to dance at Asuka Lane in Tokyo.
Heika Saito, who used to dance with me, gave me one of her dances.
I am the new born member of Sakurazaka 46.
It has always been my dream to come to Tokushima Prefecture and dance with Heika Ozawa, so my dream came true.
I am also very happy to hear that Karen-san is going to dance with me.
Thank you very much.
Since she came all the way here, she changed her clothes and even danced with me once.
I am very happy. This is a performance.
Now, I'm going to change. I look forward to working with you.
Don't worry about getting all stiff.It's okay if you've hardened it a lot.
The spray thing.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
I've never seen purple before.
Your hair looks beautiful.
It looks great on you.
I had an image of a cool lady.
I was like...
From my point of view
Purple image.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh!
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Ta-da!
Yes...
I've never danced in the nude before, and I've always admired it.
I remember how cool it was to see the ladies dancing in the nude, so today will be my first time.
So today, for the first time, I will dance in the nude.
So today, for the first time, I'm going to dance naked.
I used to wear a red happy like this, the children's red happy.
I miss it so much!
Good night, Mr. Ohkun.
Good night, Mr. Okun.
Good night.
Good night, baby.
Good night, good night, good night.
Good night, good night, good night, good night, good night.
He is very nervous.
I'm in a state of absentmindedness
Gums so dry
My front teeth have hardened so much
I'm so proud of him!
I'm so proud of you.I knew it!
I just participated in one long leg.
I don't even know if I was smiling or not.
I could not even tell if I was smiling or not.
I started to remember what I was warned about in the past
I started to remember what I was warned about in the past.
I'm going to participate in the main event after this.
I'm going to dance again, and I'm going to enjoy it.
The first one is bad. The difference in sound. I wonder why.
Also, may I ask you to join us just for the sound?
The sound.
The current one.
About the first one.
Oh, oh, I found a toy for you.
Okkun, I found a toy for you.
Ojahee, I'm here!
Ha-ha-ha!
It's raining so hard!
It's kind of yucky, isn't it?
It's so bad, it's so bad.
So many people in the city.
If you become friends with many people
Fun!
Cute!
People called me just now.
I was hungry.
So cute.
It's my heart.
I'd like to try again
I can't believe this big pudding dances.
It's so cute
I wonder if this big pudding
Do you see it often?
It's so cute!
Cutecute
cute
Cute.
I'm tired. Cute.
Maybe you know some of them.
I just had a chance to see the Zarei-hen from the outside for the first time.
Everyone was so beautiful and cool that I forgot about the rain.
They were so sparkling that they didn't look like the people I just talked to.
I'm a little nervous now to be among them.
But I'm looking forward to it.
It's been a while since I've danced outside.
I'm looking forward to it.
After you started at the house...
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
Soon, then.
Yes, sir.
Yes. How's it going? Oh, my God.
Pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre.
Puripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuri.
How do you like it?
Oh, my God!
If you're alone and looking in a different direction or something, you'll probably be alone for the rest of your life
I'll never be able to break my win, sob, sob, sob
I'm going to be on YouTube for the rest of my life.
I'm going to enjoy it because I'm already feeling this way.
I'm scared because I really liked this road at night.
Thank you very much for watching.
On the day of the entrance exam in Tokyo, there was a prayer.
I was riding on the wings of a big bird there,
Prayer guests...
We got through this big cloud.
So, what are you doing in Osaka?So, like, what are you doing in Osaka?
The guests who are dreaming
Riding on the wings of the great bird together
We are cheering for everyone's prayers
at last!
President Kato
Ohtori no Hane, what are you doing in Osaka
We support your prayers.
Thank you for watching.
Chiyo's energetic little dance
And following that
Kirei no yoichi sama maki
Momo on the women's happi dancing in style
White and well Yuda de
The women dance in a glamorous manner
The movement of the beat is like a net being pulled in
This male dance of the five snake soldiers
It is said to be called "Amiuchi
They tie their three arms together
Let's dance quickly
Let's dance, dance, dance!
Let's dance!
Let's dance, dance, dance
Kukage-roku kukage
Kugake-rokuge
Let's dance the sasari danceQuickly, quickly, dance!
Come on!
Quickly!
Faster, faster, faster
Faster!
Find it
Yuka was fixing it, so I thought it was really cool.
I did it! This is a YouTube video that will make you cry!
Seriously, what I said was true happened.
I turned around and they all turned this way.
It's going to be so much fun. We'll be loud together.
It's really the only part where I made a mistake.
It's impossible.
It's really impossible.
Everyone is so beautiful and so well put together.
Mr. A's dance was...
I turned it over by myself.
It was time for a break.
It's time to cry
I bought a shrimp sponge cake
The next one will finally be the last
I hope the day will go by more and more quickly
I hope I have no regrets in the end
I'm going to enjoy myself and dance a lot so that I don't have any regrets
I'm off now!
See you soon!
The graceful and graceful dance of a woman
First appearance at Tokushima's Awamodori!
Ms. Kyuka Saito of Sakurazaka Hokey Tinks is also dancing this year!
Thank you for allowing me to participate in Omori in Tokushima.
I really enjoyed participating today and would be happy to participate again.
Thank you so much for your time in the rain. Please continue to have fun.
The dancer next to me is Toyosaka Saito of The Flash 46.
We sold a lot of T-shirts, so it was a lot of fun to see the rest of the locations where we took pictures.
I'd love to see some humming that goes with the nice weather.I would also like to see some humming that matches the nice weather.
This is the end kama Torch-Flash sorry for buy interesting things.
All the jokes are wikimoro.
My heart is floating too
floating and dancing, bubbling and dancing
Hahaha, finally
Yes, yes, yes, yes, finally
Finally... Finally...
Bubble dance
Bubbles, bubbles, bubbles
Bubbles dancing
HAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAY
Finally... finally...
Finally...
All the guests
I have to get over here.
I'll be out of here at 8:00.
Thank you very much.
Today, I danced beside the leader of the company for the last time.
He was a very good dancer.
But after dancing with all of you together...
I thought my dance was beautiful.
I have always wanted to dance with you.
If you dance with me again
I would be happy to dance with you again.
Thank you very much.
I will practice so that I can dance with confidence.
Yes, so...
The last week, I went to Tokushima prefecture
The video of my abodori ride is
It comes to an end!It's the end!
It was really raining hard, but everyone was so kind.
And most of all, I had a really good time.
I am very satisfied!
I'm really happy with Abodori because it's the best!
I hope everyone will give me their predictions for Abodori!
I hope you all have a great time at Abodori!
Yes, I mean it.
Thank you so much! And Kotani-san.
Thank you so much!
If you like this video, please subscribe to our channel!
Abodori is the best!
I was talking about Hashimaki the other day.
I don't know what it is because we don't have anything called Hashimaki in Kanto.
When we were talking about it, the mother of a little boy from Gogerhellen told us that her mother bought it for her.
She asked me to buy some for her and eat it quickly!
I've been so wrapped up in kindness all day today.
It's raining so hard, it's coming out!
Tears, my tears...
Oh!
Okonomiyaki? I heard it's wrapped in okonomiyaki.
It's so delicious!
I'll definitely make a mistake next time!
Mmmmmm...
Thank you. It's delicious.